Guide to the Eugene B. Dynkin papers, 1950-2014.
Dynkin, Eugene B. papers,
- Series I. Author Files
  - Subseries Ib. Alphabetical Files, group 2
    - Williams, David, 1964-1974 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Wolfowitz, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Yanovskaya, Sofya, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Yor, Marc, 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous publications, Undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Series II. Publications by Eugene B. Dynkin
  - Subseries IIa. Chronological publications
    Numbers correspond to publication list in box 10, folder 15
    - List of publications of Eugene B Dynkin II, Research Papers, Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Selected papers of E.B. Dynkin with commentary, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - 1-3, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - 4-6, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - 7-9, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - 10-15, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - 16-19, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - 20-23, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - 24-30, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - 31-38, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - 39-43, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - 44, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - 45-49, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 50-54, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 55-56, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - 58-59, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - 60-61, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - 62, 64, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - 65-66, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - 67-68, 69, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - 70-72, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 73-77, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - 78-80, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - 81-82, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - 83-90, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 13-14)
    - 91, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - 92-93, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - 94-98, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - 99-101, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - 102-104, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - 105, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - 106-107, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - 108-109, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - 110-111, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - 112-113, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - 113-132, 1982-1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Removed from labelled binder
    - 114-118, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - 119-121, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - 122-124, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - 125-127, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - 128-129, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - 130-132, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - 133-136, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      Includes correspondence.
    - 133-141, 1989-1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - 137-139, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - 140-141, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - 142-144, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - 142-157, 1993-1997 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - 145-146, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - 147-148, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - 149-152, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - 153-157, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - 158-162, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - 158-169, 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - 163-166, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - 167-170, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - 170-185, 2001-2010 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - 171, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - 172-173, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - 174-175, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - 176-178, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - 179-181, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - 182-186, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Series IIb. Publications and related material
    - Publications, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Publications, Undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
      Some contain edits
    - Publication with remarks, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Publication with edits, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Research papers abstracts, 1945-2005 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Book publication lists and google citations, Undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Books, Miscellania (math reviews), ISI citation (summary), 1952-2004 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - ISI citation (full record), 1998 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Russian math publications, with Dynkin, 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Russian math publications, with Dynkin, 1970-1972 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Mamemamu publication, Undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Russian math publications, 1965-1979 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Russian and English math publications, 1966-1992 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Russian and English math publications, 1961-1998 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Series III. Research Material and Notes
  - Notes, 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Notes, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Notes, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Notes, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Notes, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Notes, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Notes, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Notes, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Notes, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Notes, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 15-16)
  - Notes, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Notes, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
  - Notes, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Notes, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Notes, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Notes, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 7-8)
  - Notes, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Notes, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Notes, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Notes, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 12-13)
  - Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Notes, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Notes, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Notes, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Notes, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Notes, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Notes, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Notes, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Notes, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Notes, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Notes, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Notes, 1965-1983 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Series IV. Talks and Conferences
  - Nankai, 1988-12-1989-01 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Rome, 1988-06 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Oberwolfuch, 1988-10-27 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Beijing, 1988-12-1989-01 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - La Jolla, 1989-03 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - University of Maryland, 1989-04-25 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Cornell University, 1989-05-14 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Zurich, 1989-06-05 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Russia, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Lecture transparencies, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Vancouver, 1990-05-10 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - UCSD, 1991-01-1991-03 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Irvine, 1991-02 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Zurich, 1991-04-1991-07 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Wald, 1991-08 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Montreal, 1992-01 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Brown, 1992-04-10 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Barrett Memorial Lectures, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - St. Petersburg, 1993-06 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Cornell University, 1993-07-1993-09 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - MSI, 1993-10-18 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Taiwan, 1993-11-03 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Cornell University, 1994-05-22 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Montreal, 1994-10 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Minneapolis, 1995-01 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Mittag-Leffler Institute, 1995-05 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Lecture notes, 1995-05-1995-06 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Stockholm, 1995-05-23 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Sweden, Michigan, Wayne SU, 1996-06-1996-10 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - La Jolla, 1997-01 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Paris, 1997-02-25 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University, 1997-09-08 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - MSRI, 1997-09-16 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University, 1998-03-30 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Rostock, 1998-08 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Lecture transparencies, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Berlin, 1999-01-13 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Bielefeld, 1999-01-15 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Leipzig, 1999-01-18 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Penn State, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Minneapolis, 2001-05-25 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Probability Seminar, 2002-09-23 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - MIT, 2003-02-12 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Paris, 2003-03-11 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Syracuse, 2003-04-05 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Maryland, 2003-05-25 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Moscow, 2003-06-17 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Cornell University, 2003-09-15 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Lecture transparencies, 2004-2006 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Abel Symposium, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Sophus Lie days, 2006-04 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Paris, 2006-07 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Lecture transparencies, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Karpelevich, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Lecture transparencies, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Boulder, 2010-06 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Series V. Course Material
  - Subseries Va. Cornell
    - Math 280B, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Math 412, 1986-02-1986-05 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Math 413, 1986-09-1986-12 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Math 413, 1991-12 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Math 413, 1994-08-1995-12 (Box 27, Folder 43-44)
    - Math 414, 1981-02-1981-05 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Math 414, 1992-01-1992-05 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Math 418, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Math 418, 1978-02-1978-05 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Math 418, 1980-1988 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Math 418, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Math 418, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Math 418, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Math 418, 2002-01-2002-05 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Math 471, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Math 511 (611), 1985-1992 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Math 511 (611), 2008 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Math 511 (611), 2002 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Math 521, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Math 571 (671), 1976 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Math 571 (671), 1977 (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Math 571 (671), 1979 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Math 571 (671), 1982 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Math 571 (671), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Math 571 (671), 1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Math 571 (671), 1993 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Math 571 (671), 1997 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Math 571 (671), 2001 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Math 571 (671), 2005 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Math 571 (671), 2009 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Math 572 (672), 1980-1993 (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - Math 572 (672), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Math 572 (672), 1979 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Math 572 (672), 1994 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Math 572 (672), 1998 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Math 572 (672), 2002 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Math 572 (672), 2004 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Math 572 (672), 2006 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Math 572 (672), 2008 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Math 611, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Math 621, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Math 649, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Math 649, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - Math 649, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 65-66)
    - Math 650, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Math 712, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Math 677 Stochastic processes, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Math 677 Random fields, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Math 677 Greens spaces, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Math 677 Random fields, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Math 677/678 superprocesses, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Math 678 Erdogic Theory, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Math 678 Processes and fields, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Math 678, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Math 678, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Math 678, 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Math 778, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Math 778, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Lecture transparencies, Undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Lecture notes, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Lecture notes, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Lecture notes and transparencies, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Lecture notes, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Subseries Vb. Moscow
    - Introductory lecture, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Fall, 31 lectures, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Spring, 28 lectures, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Fall, 23 lectures, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Spring, 20 lectures, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Moscow notes, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Moscow notes, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Moscow notes, 1957-1966 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Moscow seminars, Undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Series VI. The Situation in Soviet Mathematics
  - Subseries VIa. General documents
    - The Situation in Soviet Mathematics notes and correspondence, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Math in Russia clippings, 1980-1993 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Math in Russia clippings, 1999-2009 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Math in Russia clippings, Undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Antisemitism in Soviet Math publications, 1979-1982 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Includes some correspondence on the book
    - "Bad Guys" I, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      Information on Soviet mathematician visits
    - "Bad Guys" II, 1980-1992 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Final version of article, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Drafts, Undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Coauthors, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Sponsors, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Ximchenko, N.G, Undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Subseries VIb. Russian mathematicians biographies and articles
    Removed from labelled binders
    - Russian mathematician biographies and clippings, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Mathematicians A-L, Undated (Box 23, Folder 9-10)
      Biographies and bibliographies
    - Mathematicians M-Z, Undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Information on mathematicians, Undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
      Includes images and information on interviews
    - Bonyer, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Brezis, Undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Brezis, Marcus, and Ponce (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Gorelik, G., 2005 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Gorodov, Turnir, Undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Grothendieck, Alexander (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Marcus and Veron, Undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Mekhmat, 2000-2002 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Oshima, Toshio, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      One article is within the book boards of "The Plainsman, 1948", which contains many signatures.
    - Perkins, Edwin, Undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Shararevich, Undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Shenderovich, Victor, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Slansky, R, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Solzhenitsin, 1998-2003 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Veron, Laurent, Undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Wentzell, Alexander, Undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Series VII. General Documents
  - Interview transcripts, 1978-2004 (Box 33, Folder 20-22)
  - LIE manual, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - LIE publications, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - LIE groups and physics, Undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Google analytics, 2012-2013 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Cornell hiring needs and mailers, 2010-2012 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Russian correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - National Academy correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - American Academy correspondence, 1978-2014 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Genealogy tree of Dynkins School, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - School No. 2, 1950-2003 (Box 33, Folder 15-16)
    Includes photographs.
  - School No. 2 fund, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Ithaca High School mini math, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Lablst, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Series VIII. Personal and Biographical Material
  - Degrees and tenure information, 1952-1989 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Awards and certificates, 1951-2012 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Passports, 1978-2002 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Postcards, Undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - "Life in Mathematics", 2012 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - "70 years in Mathematics", Undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Dynkins bios, publication lists, and CV, 2001-2012 (Box 33, Folder 11-12)
  - Book contracts and royalties, 2001-2004 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Includes some paper edits
  - Signed card with many signatures from Tomoko Yamada, 1981-09 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Day books and address cards, 1976-1986 (Box 35)
  - Address cards and bibliography cards, Undated (Box 36)
  - Russian medal, 2006; MU-2475 (Box 36)
  - Signed birthday card with stamps, Undated (Mapcase-folder 1)
- Series IX. Audio/Visual material
  - Subseries IXa. Cassettes
    - Numbered 1-80, order by Dynkins
      - Yanovskaya, Sofya; Baryelb, Mischa, Undated; tr-17291 (Box 34)
        cassette
      - Baryelb, Mischa; Karpelevich, 1975-1978; tr-17292 (Box 34)
      - Yanovskaya, Sofya, 1960-1967; tr-17293 (Box 34)
      - Kolmogorov, 1966; tr-17294 (Box 34)
      - Galich, Undated; tr-17295 (Box 34)
      - Kendall; Polbsha, 1969; tr-17296 (Box 34)
      - Doob, Joseph; Walsh, John; Rosenblatt, Murray; Foata, Dominique; Garsia, Adriano; Halkin, Hubert; Kac, Mark; Durrett, Richard; Ito, Kiyoshi, 1978; tr-17297 (Box 34)
      - Orlov, Mitya; Kac, Victor, Undated; tr-17298 (Box 34)
      - Vanderbei, Accardi; Novodvorsky, Shiryaev, 1978; tr-17299 (Box 34)
      - Tintner, Gerhard; Piatetski-Shapiro, Ilya, 1978; tr-17300 (Box 34)
      - Shusterovich, 1982; tr-17301 (Box 34)
      - Kendall, David, 1979; tr-17302 (Box 34)
      - Snell, J. Laurie, 1980-05-08; tr-17302 (Box 34)
      - Katok; Ershov; Levin, 1979; tr-17303 (Box 34)
      - Kifer, Yuri; Novodvorksy, M.; Taksar; Ligget, 1977-1979; tr-17304 (Box 34)
      - Getoor, Ronald; Snell, J.Laurie, 1980; tr-17305 (Box 34)
      - Williams, D., 1979; tr-17305 (Box 34)
      - Vaserstein, Leonid, 1979-1980; tr-17306 (Box 34)
      - Weiss, Benjamin, 1976; tr-17306 (Box 34)
      - Lewis, J.; Eckmann, Beno; Nagasawa, Misao, 1980; tr-17306 (Box 34)
      - Nagasawa, Misao; Follmer, Hans; Chung, Kai Lai; Donsker, Monroe, Undated; tr-17307 (Box 34)
      - Donsker, Monroe; Fukushima; Taylor J, Katok, 1980; tr-17308 (Box 34)
      - Katok, Anatole, 1981-01; tr-17309 (Box 34)
      - Katok, Anatole and Svetlana; Vanderbei, Robert, 1981; tr-17310 (Box 34)
      - Vanderbei, Robert; Mandelbrot, Benoit, 1981; tr-17311 (Box 34)
      - Katsenelinboigen, Aron, 1981-07-05; tr-17312 (Box 34)
      - Katok, Svetlana, Undated; tr-17312 (Box 34)
      - Okudjava's songs, 1981-03-30; tr-17312 (Box 34)
      - Ropert, Ida, 1981-05; tr-17312 (Box 34)
      - Friedman, Avner, 1978; tr-17312 (Box 34)
      - Walsh, John; Maisonneuve, Bernard, 1981; tr-17313 (Box 34)
      - Tokyo, 1977; tr-17313 (Box 34)
      - Lewy, Hans; Orey, Steven, 1981-10-07; tr-17314 (Box 34)
      - Kupisk, Vitaly, 1982-11-03; tr-17314 (Box 34)
      - Sheppard, Patrick, 1982-11-15; tr-17314 (Box 34)
      - Trakhtenbrot, Boris, 1981-10-18; tr-17315 (Box 34)
      - Voronel, Alexander, 1981-12-14; tr-17315 (Box 34)
      - Ginlar and Prabhu, 1982-02-28; tr-17316 (Box 34)
      - Lewy, Hans, Undated; tr-17316 (Box 34)
      - Meyer, P.A., 1982-01-09; tr-17316 (Box 34)
      - Yessenin-Volpin, 1982-06-29; tr-17316 (Box 34)
      - Indian Diary, 1982-01-11; tr-17316 (Box 34)
      - Argentina, Brazil, 1981; tr-17317 (Box 34)
      - Argentina, 1981; tr-17318 (Box 34)
      - India, 1982; tr-17318 (Box 34)
      - Spivakovsky, Mark; Kitaigorodskii, S.A., 1982; tr-17319 (Box 34)
      - Freiman, Gregory, Undated; tr-17320 (Box 34)
      - Freiman, Gregory, 1982; tr-17321 (Box 34)
      - Shapiro, Alexander, 1983; tr-17321 (Box 34)
      - Freiman, Gregory "Departure from the USSR", 1983-11-18; tr-17322 (Box 34)
      - Levin, Leonid, 1982-12-06; tr-17323 (Box 34)
      - Brydges, David, 1982-10-06; tr-17323 (Box 34)
      - Bosky, Dmitri, 1982-12-25; tr-17323 (Box 34)
      - Watkins, J. and Faulkner, Neil, 1984-03-31; tr-17324 (Box 34)
      - Bosky, Dmitri, Undated; tr-17324 (Box 34)
      - Walsh, John, 1984-03-27; tr-17325 (Box 34)
      - Shiryaev, Albert, 1984-10-08; tr-17326 (Box 34)
      - Barlow, Martin, 1984-11-04; tr-17327 (Box 34)
      - Norris, James, Undated; tr-17327 (Box 34)
      - Norris, James, 1984; tr-17328 (Box 34)
      - Kac, Mark, 1978; tr-17329 (Box 34)
      - Glover, J; Rosen, J., 1987-01; tr-17330 (Box 34)
      - Rogers; Iscoe; Reznik, 1986; tr-17331 (Box 34)
      - Freidlin, Mark, 1987-05-22; tr-17332 (Box 34)
      - Freidlin, Mark, 1987-05-22; tr-17333 (Box 34)
      - Dawson; Harris; Le Gall, 1987; tr-17334 (Box 34)
      - Kagan, Abram, 1988-05-22; tr-17335 (Box 34)
      - Shepp, Lawrence; Yaglom, Akiva, 1988-10-17; tr-17336 (Box 34)
      - Kagan, Abram, 1988-05-22; tr-17337 (Box 34)
      - Yushkevich, Alexander, 1989-03-14; tr-17337 (Box 34)
      - Yaglom, Akiva; Yushkevich, Alexander; Kovalev, Sergei Adamovich, 1989-03-14; tr-17338 (Box 34)
      - Dobrushin, Roland; Kuznetsov, Sergei, 1989; tr-17339 (Box 34)
      - Kuznetsov, Sergei; Uspenskiy, Vladimir, 1990; tr-17340 (Box 34)
      - Evstigneev, Igor; Wentzell, Alexander, Undated; tr-17341 (Box 34)
      - Wemtzell, Alexander, 1989-09; tr-17342 (Box 34)
      - Vinberg, Ernest; Movshovich, Solomon, 1989-09; tr-17343 (Box 34)
      - Karpelevich, Fridrikh; Yushkevich, Alexander, 1989; tr-17344 (Box 34)
      - Kirillov, Alexandre; Volkonsky, Victor; Vvedenskaya, Nikita, 1989; tr-17345 (Box 34)
      - Kuznetsov, Sergei; Vvedenskaya, Nikita, 1989; tr-17346 (Box 34)
      - Vvendeskaya, Nikita, 1989; tr-17347 (Box 34)
      - Shkila, Undated; tr-17348 (Box 34)
      - Vvendeskaya, Nikita, 1989-12-11; tr-17349 (Box 34)
      - Toom, Andrei; Vershik, Anatoly, 1990; tr-17350 (Box 34)
      - Molchanov, Stanislav; Sidorenko, Alexander, 1989; tr-17351 (Box 34)
      - Vershik, Anatoly, 1990; tr-17352 (Box 34)
      - Vershik, Anatoly; Orlov, Yuri, 1990; tr-17353 (Box 34)
      - Menshikov, Mikhail, Undated; tr-17354 (Box 34)
      - Adelson-Velsky, Georg; Shkola, 1990; tr-17355 (Box 34)
      - Shkola; Landis, Evgenii, 1990; tr-17356 (Box 34)
      - Landis, Evgenii, 1990; tr-17357 (Box 34)
      - Zolotarev, Vladimir; Malyutov, Mikhail, 1990; tr-17358 (Box 34)
      - Shubin, Mikhail, Undated; tr-17359 (Box 34)
      - Kirillov, Alexandre, 1990; tr-17360 (Box 34)
      - Shubin, Mikhail; Ganago, Alexander, 1991; tr-17361 (Box 34)
      - Shubin, Mikhail; Ganago, Alexander; Krylov, Nicolai, 1991; tr-17362 (Box 34)
      - Krylov, Nicolai; Skorokhod, Anatoliy, 1991-1992; tr-17363 (Box 34)
      - Kaimanovich, Vadim, 1992-06-07; tr-17371 (Box 34)
      - Uzkoye, 1993-04-08; tr-17371 (Box 34)
      - Vinberg, Ernest; Skorokhod, Anatoliy, 1992; tr-17372 (Box 34)
      - Gordina, Maria; Ovseevich, 1993; tr-17364 (Box 34)
      - Tikhomirov, Vladimir, 1993; tr-17365 (Box 34)
      - Tikhomirov, Vladimir; Vershik, Anatoly, 1993; tr-17366 (Box 34)
      - Kuznetsov, Sergei, 1993; tr-17367 (Box 34)
      - Baryashev, Ya., 1993; tr-17368 (Box 34)
      - Dynkins, Eugene, 1993; tr-17369 (Box 34)
      - Wentzell, Alexander, 1998; tr-17370 (Box 34)
    - Cassettes not numbered by Dynkin
      - English Schools, Undated; tr-17373 (Box 34)
      - Swansea, New Orleans, Barbour, Kelly, Undated; tr-17374 (Box 34)
  - Subseries IXb.Videos
    - Tomaso, etc., Undated; v-10956 (Box 35)
      VHS
    - Optimal Choice, Montreal, 1993-01-13; v-10957 (Box 35)
    - Probability and PDE, Warwick, 1995-06-09; v-10958 (Box 35)
    - [Illegible title], Undated; v-10959 (Box 35)
    - Beijing, Changsha, Zhang Jia Jie, S. Watanabe, 1999-08; v-10960 (Box 35)
    - Katok, Berest, Kabatiansky, Rosenfeld, Penn state, 1999-2000; v-10961 (Box 35)
    - Katok, 1999; v-10962 (Box 35)
    - Sheu (with family), 2000; v-10963 (Box 35)
    - Yaglom, Akiva; Gross, 2002; v-10963 (Box 35)
    - Romanova, Maria; Margulis, Grigory; Spiridonov, 2001; v-10964 (Box 35)
    - Penn State and others, 2000; v-10965 (Box 35)
    - Home, Warwick, Sweden, Minnesota, 1995-1996; v-10966 (Box 35)
    - Dynkins, Undated; v-10967 (Box 35)
    - Jubilee Banquet, 1994; v-10968 (Box 35)
    - Jubilee Reunion, 1994; v-10969 (Box 35)
    - Paris VI, 1997-02-26; v-10969 (Box 35)
    - Dynkins, Undated; v-10970 (Box 35)
    - Foellmer, Hans and Molina; Voevoskich, Undated; v-10971 (Box 35)
    - Home, Le Gall, Wentzells, ID, Gorodetsky, Spiridonovs, Undated; v-10972 (Box 35)
    - Home, Malyutov, Shnol, Ilyashenko, Spiridonovs, Undated; v-10973 (Box 35)
    - Ido Sentyabrv, others, 1998-2002; v-10974 (Box 35)
    - Kathys Wedding, 1997; v-10975 (Box 35)
    - Birthday Party, Evstigneev, Gabrielov, 1999; v-10976 (Box 35)
    - Home, Spiridonovs, Vinberg, Artemov-Nogins, 1999; v-10977 (Box 35)
    - Probability and PDE, History and Recent Progress, Warwick, 1995-06-09; v-10978 (Box 35)
      VHS-C
    - Paris, Ithaca, 1997; v-10979 (Box 35)
    - IGD, 1999-08; v-10980 (Box 35)
    - EBD at home, 1999; v-10981 (Box 35)
    - 70 Years Jubilee Reunion, Party, 1994-05; v-10982 (Box 35)
    - 70 Years Jubilee Banquet, 1994-05-23; v-10983 (Box 35)